I like your hard work.
Hallo! Stee, this time we have with us Kisora Niinuma from Tsubaki Factory and Yumi Kasai from Tsubaki Factory!
These two will be presenting this time, so please bear with me until the end!
Now, this "Halo! Ste will be distributed on August 23rd, so tomorrow, August 24th, Tsubaki Factory's Summer Festival 2023 Burning Hot will finally be held!
It's going to be held on August 24th, and it's going to be held on August 24th.
Burning Heat was held for the first time last year.
It was held for the first time last year.
We are very happy to announce that we will be able to hold it again this year.
We are also
We're very enthusiastic about it.
than last year.
We are planning to make it a more powerful event
I hope you are looking forward to it.
I hope you can look forward to it.
Yumi, you are also from Yamanashi, right?
Yes, I am. That's right. So I'm really fired up, so please come.
Please come.
And I have an announcement from Tsubaki Factory.
Tsubaki Factory will be holding an autumn tour.
Please come and see the current Tsubaki Factory.
And on September 27, Tsubaki Factory's new single
It's my life! It's my life!
All three songs are full of charm, so please check them out.
Tsubaki Factory's first overseas performances will be held in Hong Kong and Taiwan.
We will do our best to let people overseas know about Tsubaki Factory.
Please take a look at this video. Here you go! Album Theme Song Album Theme Song Album Theme Song Album Theme Song Album Theme Song Album Theme Song
Album Theme Song Album Theme Song Album Theme Song
Album Theme Songs Album Theme Songs Album Theme Songs
Album Theme Song Album Theme Song Album Theme Song Album Theme Song Album Theme Song Album Theme Song Album Theme Song That's Virgo KinsandanAlbum Theme Song Album Theme Song Album Theme Song Album Theme Song Album Theme Song Album Theme Song Album Theme Song That's the Virgo Gold and Silver
The river on the beach The galaxy Orion is
Land of the Solar System Three Planets
All of them
I want to lose a little more weight, defying gravity, the maiden's heart
Dharma
I love you.
The heart is the position The image of love
It All Started From Nothing
Running Running Running Big Bang
If I told you it was in the city
I don't want to die
Three hundred thousand miles per second
Even light can't break free
I Want It Too Heavy
Two hearts
Who's there? Who's there? Who's there? Who's there? Who's there? Who's there?
What, what, what? Don't bother me now
I can't believe that I'm the only one who's really desperate
Because I only love you
Hearts are all messed up, love's inbetween
Like a star circling around 10,000 miles
A heartbeat that could fly A big band of light
I've got to cancel our date.
I never went home.
Born in space, one hundred and eighty billion years
In your arms
I'm so happy.
Next time, next time, where shall we go?
Next time, next time, next time, what should we eat?
I love you, don't I?
My heart is expanding
In a galaxy of love invasion and destruction
Fall in love with someone
My darling, my star
Galaxy in loveA Galaxy in Love
A boy, yes
Across time and space
I'll see you in the great night sky
The time that is far away
Harukanaru Hibi (Days Far Away)
Sora Niimaki of Ah Ganbarou Tsubaki Factory and Yumi Kasai of Tsubaki Factory present Halo! Stay!
I'm going to ask you some questions, so please answer them quickly and without thinking too much.
I'm going to ask you a few questions, so please think fast and answer at your own pace.
What do you recommend for a good night's sleep during this difficult season?
A cold mat.
Tomorrow, Yumi Kasai will be in her hometown, Yamanashi.
Tsubaki Factory's summer festival 2023 Shaku-etsu will be held tomorrow in her hometown Yamanashi.
Where do you recommend to go before and after the live?
Marusawa Hyoketsu
What does Yumi Kasai most want to express right now?
Yumi as a 20 year old adult
What is your favorite summer memory at Tsubaki Factory?
Watermelon splitting.
This year marks the 25th anniversary of Hello! Project celebrates its 25th anniversary this year. What song would you like to perform on stage at least once?
Crying Boy
Oh!
Thank you.
So, I would like to ask you what I am interested in,
First of all, I'm going to visit Yamanashi Prefecture for the Shaku-etsu to be held tomorrow,
What do you recommend there?
Narusawa Hyoketsu.
What kind of place is it?
It is like a cave, and it is very cold when you go inside, but there is ice inside,
The ice is lit up and I thought it was perfect for this time of year, so I thought I would recommend it.
I thought it was perfect for this time of year, so I thought I would recommend it.
You can go there to cool off.
It looks like it's very cold.
They sell soft-serve ice cream and other things near there, so it's a famous tourist spot,
I would like everyone to go there.I would like everyone to try it.
And what is it that Yumi Kasai wants to express the most? I'd like to ask you that,
You turned 20 years old last month, right?
That's right. So, up until now, I have been trying to give a fresh and powerful performance, which is a bit serious,
From now on, I would like to try my best to give a slightly more mature performance.
So, we can expect to see many different Yumi's at age 20,
I am looking forward to seeing you in many different ways.
Questions for Ms. Shinnuma will come after the VTR.
Hallo! Stu Stu Stu Pride Bright Now on sale!
Oh Let's play Lovely Music
Let's dance Disco till morning Let's
Stu Stu Stu Funky Flossing Now on sale!
Natsu no yosei desu ka Natsu no yume kashina no chotto jojo
Buwan tei Whose fault is it?
Ocha no Obaba New Single
Chotto Jyocho Unstable Summer Now on sale!
Matcha Matcha Matcha Matcha Matcha Matcha Matcha Matcha Matcha Matcha Matcha Matcha Matcha Matcha
Zacha Zacha Zacha Zacha Zacha Zacha Zacha Zacha Zacha Zacha Zacha Zacha Zacha
Ocha no oba New Single Ocha no oba New Single
Ocha no oba Mahalo bai Koenoba
Showa and 2022 both Wachamacha Wachamacha
Now on sale
Shekena The power to believe in oneself Ordinary but forbidden
Auntie of Tea New Single
Shikenare Now on sale
Hallo! Ste.
Next, I would like to ask Shinnuma-san a question.
Yes, I will do my best.
Tomorrow 24th is Tsubaki Factory's summer festival 2023 scorching hot!
I would like to know Mr. Shinnuma's way of preventing sunburn.
It is to apply sunscreen 30 minutes before going outside.
What was the biggest shock you encountered this summer?
Not being bitten by a single mosquito.
Speaking of August, "Hitori Hitori" was released in 2016.
What is the first thing that comes to mind when you hear the title of this song?What is the first thing that comes to mind when you hear the title of this song?
Short bangs.
Where would you like to visit in the summer?
An island!
What is the first song that comes to mind when you hear the word "cute" in Hello!
Moshi Moshi!
Project's songs of all time, the song that immediately came to mind when I heard the word "cute" was "Moshi Moshi".
I thought "Moshi moshi" was the song that came to my mind,
There are many really cute songs,
The first thing that makes it cute is that it starts with a line,
I think it's really cute that the song starts with a line, and the way the words end and the way the singer sings is also really cute,
I think it is a song that Hello! Project members would want to sing at least once at a birthday event or some other event,
I have sung this song before, and I would love to see Yumi and the others sing such a cute song someday.
I will do my best.
Let's see...
Where would you like to visit in the summer?
I answered "an island.
An island? Where's an island?
Well...
I've always wanted to go to an island.
I've always wanted to go there.
And not just this summer.
I mean really this summer?
I'd like to go there someday.
Of course, I would like to visit various prefectures and foreign countries,
I'd like to go for a week or so without even touching my cell phone,
For a long period of time.
Yes.I would like to live on an hourly wage and be self-sufficient,
I hope I can make it happen someday.
Let's go together.
I feel like I can make it work with you, and I know I can count on you,
I definitely want to take you with me.
Let's go.
So, the Hallo! I'll continue after this.So, the Hallo! Ste. It will continue after this.
This is Matsuyaki-Miyabe. So, Hallo! Ste will continue after this. Hallo! Ste. Conversion
This is Masashi Natsuyaki.
Here we go. Hello Kitchen.
This time, we have this member here.
This is Ayano Kawamura from Angelem.
I will do my best. I look forward to working with you.
Please give my best regards, Ms. Kawamura. I look forward to working with you.
Now, what shall we make this time?
Yes, this way today.
Oh!
Bonito
Bonito.
I had this cutlass cut for me.
Nigirizushi
Nigiri Sushi with Bonito
I'd like to try it!
Thank you very much!
This is Ayano's reserver here.
for the
Thank you very much!
I heard that Ayano-chan has done a tuna demolition show in the past.That's right.
She's a certified first-class tuna dismantler.
I have done tuna dismantling shows.
So I've been carving tuna as well.
I've been cutting up a lot of skipjack since I was a child.
Since you were little?
I was born in the middle of high school, so I've been slicing bonito since I was in elementary school.
So I'm really looking forward to learning how to fillet tuna from the instructor today.
Let's do our best!
So, Sensei, what shall we do first?
So we're going to cook rice, and we're going to have 2 cups of rice and 2 cups of water.
So we're going to cook 2 cups of rice and 2 cups of water, and we're going to use the rice cooker button.
I'm going to press it here.
Bleep.Beep.
Yes, I'm fine.
Now then, let's move on.
Next, we're going to cut up some bonito.
Right away!
Ayano, you're going to show off.
I'm looking forward to it.
You prepared the cutting board, didn't you?
That's amazing.
The teacher prepared the cutting board, and...
And you...
I'll get the knife.
Shall we cut the bonito then?
Yes, please.
May I?
Here you go.
please. Yes, please.
It's huge!
That's great.
I'm used to it.
Ayano-chan is leading this time.
I can lower my body, but I don't think I'm a match for you.
But I'm sure the two of you can really get this done together.
It's really cool.
I'm left-handed, so when I watched the videos, they were all reversed, so it was hard for me to remember.
Everything is reversed, but when I learn dances and stuff, I learn by judging.
I learn by judging.
You use that ability.
You ask yourself questions, don't you?
Yes, I ask myself questions.That's cool.
How old were you when you were little?
You seem to be having the hardest time right now.
This part is pretty important.
There you go.
Yes, sir.Yes, sir.
And the belly.
Put it in.
If you cut the belly here...
Yes, the entrails.
Don't cut this.
The entrails will come out.
I see.
That's how you do it.
To cut a little bit off the chiai.
Well, anyway, the thick part of the chiai...
I cut off the thickest part of the chiai with a knife.
If you just pour off the thousand, it'll be fine.
I see.
This is the hard part.
I guess it's more difficult here than if you go all the way through.
It's more difficult than if it went "goo" like this, but it's more difficult than if it went "goo" like this.
So you have to make cuts on both sides and peel it off.
Wow!
Wow, wow, wow!
I didn't know it could be this clean.
Let's start with the belly.
Do the stomach.
Give it back once.
I want to take this off of you, and I'll take it off of you.
Just so you can hear the bone.
I'm cutting the inside bone now.
Oh, wow.
Listen to the sound of the bone.
Yes.
Relying on the sound of the bone.Follow the bone with the tip of the knife.
Hee...
You have to have the shape of the fish bone in your head.
I see.I know.
I'm going to go out on a limb and cheat.
That's right.
Oh!
Perfect!
Yum! Oh, my eyes!
That looks hard! So much for getting under the bone.
I don't have anything to teach you.
It's great.
This is just like the other one.
You got it, you got it, you got it, you got it.
That's a nice sound.
Yes!
It's so clean.
That's great.
Like this.
That's realistic.
I've never seen a lefty take it down before.
You know, there's a knot right here.
Yes, right here.
It's a parasite that often grows on oil.
I see.
If you think it's here, you just take it out.
May I have a word?
Maybe we should just drop him off.
There's a bone here, too.
We can take this out along with the blood.
5 pieces leaked
Wow!
Finished.
I'm done.Now, next...
Okay, now it's time to beat it!
Now, here's Miyahizu's point.
Sprinkle salt on the bonito and beat to blend.
This is a little misunderstood by everyone.I think people are a little confused about the word "whack".
You know, the real meaning of a whack.
That's right.
It's more like the locals.
Tataki is called by many kanji characters.
Tataki means "to beat the salt to make it blend
Tataki" means "to beat" in Japanese, right?
That's right.
It's not like pounding the salt in like this, but like this.
It's not like rubbing it in, but like this.
This seems to be the origin of the word "tataki".
When you put salt on meat, you usually put 1% or so of the total weight of the meat.
1% of the total weight.
But if you do that, you get too much water on this side.
I think 0.5% is a good amount.
I'll take some measurements.
1.3%.
So 0.5% is 6g
About 7g.
The berries tend to fall apart.
That's right.
The skins tend to stick, so... gentle tapping.
The skin is firm.
Put a little salt inside.
And let the water out a little.
And a little bit of the fishy smell.
The water has a fishy smell.
So it's important to remove the water.
Yes, sir.
Now, put this in the fridge.
Put it in the refrigerator.
And let it cool.
During that time, the water will drain out, so it's better not to wrap it.It's better not to wrap it.
Why is that?Why is that?
Wrapping them makes it harder for moisture to escape.
The air from the fridge is still circulating in the fridge a little bit.
This will take the moisture out.
Now, I'd like to make the tai-mei.
Put it up at an angle.
Is there a special role for a coach?
I spend a lot of time on it.
Onions, for example.
That's for sure.
I'm not the wife of a sashimi chef.
If there are onions, then...
If there's onions, then you divide the meat in half, and half of it is fun, and the other half is digested with a spoon, and the other half is not.
I see... I see... I see... I feel like I have to do it this way...
You know, it's a little bit, you know, tricky.
If you take it down...
So that you can get more smell.
This is it.
Cool! What is that?
Grader?
Like a grinder.
Grader. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Be careful with it. It can go through your fingers.
If you feel a little scared, just put it down here.
Oh, I see, I see. It's safe.
That's good. How far do you want to go?
Just enough to shake it out.
Is that okay? I think that's enough.
Well, that's all for this issue.
Please look forward to the next installment!
It's moving, it's moving, it's moving!Bon appétit!
That's great!
Do you cook these days?
I've written about it on my blog.
I cook a lot of eggs.I've been cooking eggs a lot.
I'll say something simple.
I make fried eggs very often.
I am very particular about fried eggs.
And the whites, I don't know.
I prefer the whites to be firm, but the yolks should be half-boiled.
I like the whites hard, but I prefer the yolks half-boiled.
But I've also been into fried eggs lately.
I was trying to spread the whites the way you did,
When my grandmother made fried eggs,
When my grandmother made fried eggs, she put aluminum foil on the pan and steamed them with water inside.
So the whites hardened faster, so that's how it always was when we ate them half-boiled.
Yummy.
That's not something I've done myself. My parents make it that way, so I'd like to try it someday, and
Yumi told me that the first thing she ate when she turned 20 was a fried egg, and I remember how shocking that was for me.
I remember that as a shock to me, so I think it was fun to talk about eggs like this today.
Hello! Sta.
Next is the presentation of the lyrics that touched my heart.
Project has many lyrics that touch my heart.
Project, but right now I really like "My Days For You" by Erina Mano,
Project, but I really like Erina Mano's song "My Days For You", which says "Thank you for being here,
It's exactly as it should be,
It's a song that makes me feel that thanks to you, I am here now and I am doing my best,
I love My Days For You.
Do you have any Yumi?
I am actually in the VTR, so please check it out.
Please watch it.
The presentation of the lyrics that touched my heart!
In this corner, we will present the lyrics of Hello!
Project songs and talk about the charm of the lyrics.
I hope you, the viewers of Hello!
This week, I, Kasane, will be presenting the song.
I'm going to laugh, laugh, laugh, laugh, I'm going to cry when I'm tired, I'm going to run out with hope, I'm going to run out with a little fear...
I'm a little scared...
Smile.The lyrics of "Smile, Smile, Smile" are very cheerful...The lyrics of "Smile, Smile, Smile" are very cheerful, but I always thought it was a bit sad.
but I always thought it was a little sad somehow.
When I looked at the lyrics again
It's not just the lyrics here,
For example, she's really a serious girl,
But the image of seriousness has been created too much,
I don't think I'm that serious.
I thought the lyrics were about hiding who I really am,
Why did you choose this song?
I'm about to cry, I'm about to fly out with hope, even though I'm a little scared,
I interpreted it that way, like breaking through the sky, holding on to hope and a little bit scared, but let's break through the sky.
When we release a single, we often introduce the song in that way, and when I read the lyrics, there are a lot of things that link to us from the past.
When I read the lyrics, there were a lot of things that were linked to us in the past.
I really sympathized with the lyrics.
I like the lyrics of this song, too.
I like these lyrics, but there are other lyrics that I think are wonderful.
People are lovable because they suck at it
I heard that lyric and thought it was great that people are so lovable even if they are not very good at it. I really thought that was a wonderful lyric.
I agree.
No one can do it perfectly, so it's nice to tell people to love that part of themselves too.
If you are watching this right now, please listen to "Smile" too.
So, please look forward to the next installment.
Bye bye!
Hallo! Ste.
Kisora Arainuma of Tsubaki Factory and Yumi Kasai of Tsubaki Ctory present "Halo! STE!
It has been mentioned several times since the opening, but tomorrow, August 24, Tsubaki Factory's Summer Festival 2023
The live performance called "Burning Heat" will be held tomorrow, August 24th. The live performance called "Burning Heat" is an event that we would like to make an annual event where you can really enjoy the summer festival with us in the future.
This year's event will be more festive than last year's.
I think it will be even more summery and fun to enjoy the festival together.
Last year, we had fireworks and yukata (summer kimono), and we did all kinds of summer-related activities at the course.
This year, we may do something more summery than that,
This year, we may do something more summery than that, or we may do something that was popular last year,This year, we may do something more summery, or we may do something that was popular last year, or we may do something that we are really looking forward to and think about the set list a little bit.
We'll also have a chance to think about the set list, and we'll be able to design costumes for each of you.
It's a live performance that we create by ourselves, and we are very particular about a lot of things.
You can see how we did it on the following page.You can watch it on our sub-channel
Our sub-channel on youtube
We have a sub-channel on youtube called "Let's be happy".
on our sub-channel "Let's be happy" on youtube.
You can watch it while you watch the conference.
while watching it?
We hope you will enjoy it while watching the conference.
This year, too, we have a lot of goods,
There were also some Uchiwas, body paint stickers, and more,
We have a variety of goods this year as well, so please check them out as well.
We are also going to play a new song. Yes, we will be playing a new song. It's My Life!
It's a song that everyone who comes to the concert can enjoy together,
It's a song that everyone who comes to the event can enjoy together, so I hope you will join me in dancing to it,
I hope you will enjoy the song with everyone who comes to the event, and I hope you will imitate my dance moves.
Let's make summer memories together.
We are looking forward to seeing you.
What were you born for?
Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow
How should I live?
I make mistakes, I lie
Someone said that's what makes us human
♪ Eyes on the clouds with no desire to be more
"I'm miserable just raising my eyes above the clouds.
I've stared at people whose minds are more than the ceiling.
I stared at someone whose mind was running.
They hide their weakness with their vain attempts to hide it.
We're looking at you, too.
I don't care if he's a bastard or not.
Bad and free
Guilty.
Live your life the way you want to.
I don't care if it's just one thing
If it helps someone in some way
Moment is limited
Shine with every lifeLet's shout out our loveLet's shout out our love
Through the sorrows, the endless morels
Even if you're covered in food, just keep moving forward.
Someone will recognize you
Will notice you
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow
What you were born to do
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow
I wonder if someday you'll understand
We fight each other, we help each other
That's the mystery of human nature
We meet and we part, even if that's the rule
The thought of what we've accomplished is real
I live for myself
And if I can bring that courage to someone else...
If I could deliver it to someone else, I'd live my life to the death
Limited Moment Life is a distant hill
Limited Setting I want to cherish and nurture it, and live ..... O finite Moment, a small chance to make a dream come true
It's an unshakable dream
Limited Moment
Inherit from your friends
Beliefs that reach out
I want to connect as best I can
Endless Moment
Burning with life
A sensei to hand over to each other
I want to nurture it with care
Moment in the darkness
Pushing forward with heat
Tell them now
I heard that you made it through
I want to live
That's all Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow
What was the reason I was born
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow
Live your life to the fullestLive life to the fullest.
Thanks for your work!
This message is brought to you by Kisora Niinuma of Tsubaki Factory and Yumi Kasai of
Yumi Kasai of Tsubaki Factory presents "Halo! stay!
It's time to say goodbye!
Here's an announcement!
Project 2023 SUMMER CITY CIRCUIT will be held during the Hello! Project 2023 SUMMER CITY CIRCUIT is now underway.
This tour is even more advanced than the spring one, so I hope you will come.
And tomorrow, Tsubaki Factory's Summer Festival 2023 Scorching Heat will be held.
We are very happy to hold this event in Yamanashi Prefecture.
We are fully fired up, so please come and join us.
Tsubaki Factory's fall tour is coming soon!
And on September 27th, the new song "Organic When My Life If you're just delusional, you can be free..." will be released!
Please check it out! And Tsubaki Factory's first overseas tour has been decided.
We will be visiting Hong Kong and Taiwan.
As this is our first overseas performance, we are looking forward to meeting our overseas fans, and we will definitely do our best to let them know more about us.
In addition, on September 9 and 10, Hello Project
25th Anniversary Concert will be held on September 9 and 10.
This will be a special concert, so please come and join us! Please subscribe to our channel, as the Hello Project members will be uploading their performances on Haloste.
This time with Kisora Niinuma of Tsubaki Factory,
Yumi Kasai of Tsubaki Factory.
Good bye.
bye. you
undefined